They wrote the book on how not to be criminals.
Big Nothing is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Jean-Baptiste Andrea.
A frustrated, unemployed teacher joins forces with a scammer
and his girlfriend in a blackmailing scheme.
Charlie, played by David Schwimmer.
Gus, played by Simon Pegg.
Josie McBroom, played by Alice Eve.
Penelope Wood, played by Natascha McElhone.
Agent Hymes, played by Jon Polito.
Mrs. Smalls, played by Mimi Rogers.
Big Nothing is a 2006 black comedy crime film directed by Jean-Baptiste
Andrea, starring David Schwimmer, Simon Pegg and Alice Eve.
It had its world premiere at the Cardiff Film Festival on 18 November 2006,
and was released in the United Kingdom on 1 December 2006.
Big Nothing was filmed on the Isle of Man and in Wales at Barry in the Vale of
Glamorgan and at Caerwent and other areas of Monmouthshire.
Other scenes were at Squamish, British Columbia, Canada.
The film explores themes of blackmail, call center,
pedophile priest, oregon, usa, priest.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.